

## **NGUYEN HOANG VY**

**PHARMACIST** 



- 01649120895
- nguyenhoangvy1208@gmail.com
- Binh Thanh District, Ho Chi Minh
   City, Vietnam

### **SKILLS**

Communication

Negotiation

Team-work

- 1: 1

MS Office

### **PERSONALITY**

- Ambitious
- Enthusiastic
- Responsibility
- Self-motivated
- Well-prepared
- Working under pressure

#### **HOBBIES**

Expand relationships
Participate in extracurricular activities
Reading book and newspaper
Traveling



Take up a challenging career grows with honesty, good relationship and best performance, in order to gain experiences, skills and contribute to the development of the company.

Next 3-5 years, become a good team leader as well as an expert in this field, ready to help and

share experiences with co-worker.



## **EDUCATION**

FACULTY OF PHARMACY, DUY TAN UNIVERSITY

Degree Classification: Good, GPA = 8.04/10

INFORMATICS CERTIFICATE 2018

Certificate in basic and advanced office informatics.

TOEIC 625 BY IIG VIETNAM 2018

Valid until 03/08/2020



# **WORK EXPERIENCE**

PHARMACIST ASSISTANT

2017 - 2018

2013 - 2018

University Pharmacy, 254 Nguyen Van Linh Street, Da Nang.

Mentor: Ms.Hai Quynh, +84.918837032

Learned skills:

- Sales
- Effective communication

TUTOR 2015 - 2017

Giving instruction of Biology and psychological supports for teens.

Learned skills:

- Presentation
- Interpersonal
- Effective communication

### **WAITER AT ZAFRES COFFEE & PIZZA**

Lien Chieu District, Da Nang.

Learned skills:

- Flexibility
- Teamwork



# **OTHER ACTIVITIES**

#### ASSIST IN CONDUCTING SURVEYS REGARDING MEDICAL

2017 - 2018

2014

"Knowledge, attitude, practice about prevention of Hepatitis B of the pharmacy students at Duy Tan University."

"A knowledge attitude and behavior of pharmacy students of Duy Tan University about contraceptive methods."

CHARITY ACTIVITIES 2010 - 2016

Part of the organizers of the yearly program Moon Festival at Quang Ngai Disabled Children Education Center.

Participating in charitable activities in Dong Giang and Tay Giang - Quang Nam.

BE A MEMBER OF CEO PHARMACY DTU GROUP, DTU GUITAR CLUB, BLOOD DONATION GROUP

2014 - 2018